32/13/2018 10:07 am

It was 3 hours since my wife went missing.
//Od zaginięcia żony minęły już ponad trzy godziny.
Police stoped answering my calls,
//Policja przestała odbierać moje telefony,
probably all the forces are already looking for her.
//prawdopodobnie wszystkie siły są już skupione na
I am still scratching my head about this message
//poszukiwaniach. Ja nadal siedzę nad wiadomością,
that kidnaper left me. I only know that 
//którą zostawił porywacz. Wiem tylko, że 
he worked alone and he drove her to his mother
//był jeden i że zawiózł ją do matki,
who's apparently feeling sick. Unfortunetly I have no idea
//która ponoć źle się czuje. Niestety nie mam pojęcia
where does his mother live. He also wrote
//gdzie mieszka jego matka. Napisał również,
that he didn't want to boather me and asked me not to worry.
//że nie chciał mnie budzić i żebym się nie
Since I read that I got really worried. I think that he used some sort
//martwił. Ta informacja od początku nie dawała mi spokoju.
of sypher even though the police belive it was just a joke.
//Myślę że to szyfr, chociaż teoria policji zakłada że to żart.
And I don't know what to believe anymore. However I also noticed that
//A ja nie wiem w co wierzyć. Jednak zauważyłem również, że
her car dissapeared and I think I know where they went.
//zniknął jej samochód i zdaje mi się, że wiem którędy pojechał.



I decided to stick with that.
//Tego postanowiłem się trzymać.